Good Morning, Church!
Greet your neighbour, "Good Morning!"
Greet the viewers, "Good Morning!"
Tell your neighbour, "Neighbour, you are in the presence of God!"
Today is the day that the Lord has made.
I will rejoice and be glad in it, in Jesus‘ name.
Have your seat. Thank You, Lord.
This message today will be given in two languages: in English and French, as instructed by the Prophet.
God has made wonderful promises and they are for you, personally.
But unfortunately today, many find it difficult to believe
that God’s promise can be fulfilled in their lives.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We have a challenge today.
We are too conditioned to believe
that what we read in the Bible is for the people in the Bible alone, not for us today.
that what God says can happen to others, will not happen to us.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
It is not by power; it is not by might.
It is according to the grace of God.
By grace, Jesus met Levi, a tax collector and made him Apostle Matthew.
By grace, Jesus met a murderer sentenced to death at the cross and gave him eternal life.
By grace, Jesus met Saul, a state prosecutor and made him the great Apostle Paul.
By grace, God chose Prophet T.B. Joshua and made him a prophet to the nations,
a mentor to millions, a channel of shining light giving illumination to the whole world.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Today, by the grace of God, Jesus will change your life, if you believe.
If you believe today, the Lord will change your life in the same way, in Jesus‘ name!
God always asks us to do what we cannot do ourselves so that He can teach us how to do it.
When you allow God to transform you by the power of the Holy Spirit,
then He will literally begin to show you the way.
Then, you can know what God wants you to do and how He wants you to do it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you believe, that transforming power will change your life today.
Do you believe that?
Let someone say, 'The transforming power'.
This is our message today: 'The transforming power'.
Let’s open our Bible to the book of Genesis 1:1.
"In the beginning God created the heavens and the earth.
The earth was without form, and void; and darkness was on the face of the deep.
And the Spirit of God was hovering over the face of the waters.
Then God said, 'Let there be light‘; and there was light.
And God saw the light, that it was good; and God divided the light from the darkness.
God called the light Day, and the darkness He called Night.
So the evening and the morning were the first day.“
Good Morning to you all!
Good Morning to my life!
Good Morning to my career!
Good Morning to my destiny!
Is your life unformed and void?
Follow Jesus. Jesus is the Repairer and the Restorer.
He came to earth to transform our lives from darkness to light
and to make us partakers of the divine inheritance of the saints.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In 1 Samuel 9:21, Prophet Samuel came to anoint Saul,
and Saul answered, 'Am I not from the land of Benjamin, the least tribe of Israel?‘
When God sent the angel to Gideon to establish him as a judge of Israel,
Gideon said, 'My family is the poorest in Mannaseh‘.
He focused on his weakness; he focused on his poor family background.
When God called Moses to lead His people into the Promised Land,
Moses said, 'Lord, I cannot speak‘.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I want to tell you just one story.
One day, the Prophet preached one message and said,
"There was one disciple that was too quiet. He didn’t want to talk“.
That disciple is me; I’m the one.
I could not talk when I came here. I was too afraid to talk.
This lasted for long.
When I saw the Prophet preach, I would say, "Wow.
I will never be able to face the crowd and speak. It is too much for me“.
But glory be to God, I’m serving a man of vision.
He called me and spoke to me one day.
In class, when the Prophet said, „Who has a message?“, everybody raised their hand.
I raised my hand.
When he looked towards me, I took my hand down.
But he had seen me already.
He told me, „Ok, you are going to preach tomorrow“.
I said, „Heh? Im going to preach in the church?“
My heart started pounding.
I could not sleep the whole day.
Night closed in. I said, "Maybe Prophet just said it to test my faith".
When the time came, someone said, "Dress up. Prophet is calling you“.
I went and he said, "Are you ready? Ok, go and preach the message“.
The time I left, my heart…
I was saying, "Lord, how will I start? How will I do it?“
But the moment they gave me the mic, grace entered me.
Where God guides, He provides.
Where God guides, He provides and protects.
God Almighty oftentimes uses His messengers, servants
among those who have the least advantage of natural talent.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
How strange but wholly true, the weak, full of power the Father’s work will do.
This explains why a young, rustic and seemingly inexperienced David
could be able to defeat Goliath in representative combat.
This explains why Moses, the son of a Hebrew slave, was able to stand before Pharaoh
and proclaim the oracle of God.
This explains why people without mighty strength, fast legs, smoothness of tongue
should ever remain faithful to God for the purpose God has designed and called them for.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
It is not by power, not by might but by His grace.
Lord, I know You can change me.
Lord, I am here for the radical transformation of my life.
I know You can do it for me.
If you believe, He will do it for you today, in Jesus‘ name.
Those whom God calls for any service, He makes them fit for it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is the reason why God sent His Son, Jesus, to you and me.
Jesus Christ can change anyone – anywhere, anytime.
In John 15:3, Jesus said, 'You are already pure because of the Word I have spoken to you‘.
This means, Jesus has come to brush aside our unworthy past
and to bring us to the presence of the living Father without any sense of unworthiness.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Jesus can change anyone – anywhere, anytime.
Jesus is looking for someone to change today. Are you the one?
Begin to rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Do you believe what God said to Gideon and Saul can happen to you?
If you are too conditioned to believe that what God said cannot happen to you,
let me encourage your faith.
Success, greatness is not about our weaknesses, faults, pitfalls.
It is all about what Jesus has done for you at the Cross of Calvary.
He has made you fit and qualified you for God’s purpose in your life.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You don’t need to be perfect to be used by God. You just need to be available.
Are you available to Him? Are you available? Follow Jesus.
If you follow Him, your life will never be the same.
Jesus Christ is the same yesterday, today and forever.
Remember what he said to the disciples in Luke 10:20:
Do not rejoice that demons are subject to you but rejoice that your names are written in Heaven‘.
Knowing God is not only to see His miracles but to learn His ways.
When we learn the way of God,
then we should follow the path of faith and humility that leads to safety and eternal life.
Jesus‘ disciples followed the divine process of God.
They knew there is a time to march with God and a time to march for God.
They followed the divine principles and they met the requirement of deeper commitment to God.
And the Spirit of the Father came upon them
and made them pearls of usefulness for generations yet unborn.
They are our mirrors today.
If you want to be God’s person, follow His process.
If you want to be the man God created, follow His process.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Jesus Christ is concerned about you.
Jesus is concerned about me; Jesus is concerned about you.
God Almighty is much more interested about our future than our present state.
He knows that success has many dangers of its own.
He knows that when we come to the top, our spiritual life may gradually deterioriate.
That is why God Almighty is busy building character now
so that when you reach the place of your divine assignment,
you may not crack, explode and lose it all.
Our conduct, our character must change to agree with God’s plan for our lives.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Dedication and discipline are the fruit of victory.
Physical growth is the function of time;
intellectual growth is the function of learning
but spiritual growth is the function of obedience to God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Brethren, today is your day.
Today, we believe that the transforming power of God will make your impossibilities possible.
The Gospel of God’s grace challenges and changes everything.
To His transforming power, nothing is impossible.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
It is God’s power working through His Word by His Spirit
that brings about a new birth and a radical transformation of our lives.
How do we know the power of God?
To know God’s presence is to know His power.
How do we know the presence of God then?
The Word of God is the living presence of the divine power.
The Spirit of God will be released to the degree we stand in reverence of the Word of God.
God is with us in the living Word.
How do we know God?
We know God by the Word He speaks
and the Word God speaks represents His heart’s desire for me and for you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The Word has priority over His name.
When you take God’s Word to heart by meditation and truly make it a part of you,
it will, by its very nature, change you.
Christ’s eternal Word enables us to stop reliving the past in our present lives.
Christ’s eternal Word enables me to stop reliving the past in my present life.
When you receive the living Word in the midst of your heart,
the past will no longer control your thinking pattern, will never control your behaviour.
When you receive the living Word of Christ in the midst of your heart,
the past will no longer control your thinking pattern or your behaviour.
Then, you will begin to think not of your weakness, not of yourself
but of your righteousness in Christ Jesus.
Do you believe that?
Today, my impossibilities will become possible.
Today, I believe my life will never be the same again.
Believe the Word of God.
Trust in the Word of God and your life will never be the same.
Thank You, Jesus.
May God bless His Word.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Mel Flowers 24/12/2018